Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are up, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
After leaving Fishman Island,
the Straw Hat Pirates are making
their ascent into the new world.
The second half of the Grand Line.
Who's sailing so far?
Yeah, almost too smooth.
This feels great.
It's a technique called shower tempo.
You want to try it too?
Nah, it does look neat.
But I'm okay.
I brushed my fur two days ago.
What would really be
cool is if I could take a
bite of that fluffy cotton
candy you got there.
That's a cloud, silly. Oh, man.
It looks so sweet and yummy. Oh, my.
It seems there's something
sweet and yummy in the bathroom.
Doesn't get me more yummy than that.
That's great, Nami.
Now let's see the other side.
Chopper, you might want to move.
Yikes!
I kind of think I wanted
to eat that thing!
Perfect.
My first bath on the sunny in two years.
And it's even more luxurious with
this gorgeous underwater view.
This really is the life.
Don't they need you on
the deck to navigate?
They can take care of
things themselves as long
as I go back up before we
get to an upward current.
I might as well take my time.
I can handle a sea monster or two.
Come on, Usopp, hurry.
Just give me one more minute.
If we're going to catch a big one,
then the rope's got to be extra strong.
Oh, my. What's all this?
I was so excited to see Fishman Island on
the way down, I forgot to catch some fish.
I bet we can nab something
totally crazy down here.
And then Sanji can cook it up on the spot.
As long as it pairs well
with cola, count me here.
Seafood dinner, huh? I like it.
But if we're going to celebrate
our trip to the New World,
then I want some booze, too.
Now, which one of these
looks the tastiest?
Let's pick something really juicy.
That one would be good
fried with some salt.
Fried fish with salt, huh?
My favorite.
Or we could slice up that
skinny one and grill it.
That works, too.
How about that one?
It's nice and fat.
Let's go lay it and drown it in mayo.
Huh? This guy?
Luffy, you'll eat anything.
That creepy thing will taste like
crap no matter how you cook it.
You think so?
Meat is meat to me.
Second gear!
I could eat on that thing for
all week and still not get full.
Now gum, gum, jet pizza!
Now it's even uglier.
You sure the Sonny can carry it?
Let's find out!
Hurry and catch it! Special
attack! Capture Star!
Look there!
Jixi dinner!
Oh, man, I can't wait
to taste it! That nose.
It doesn't even look like a fish.
More like a gross old man. Kind of.
That's the end of that!
Ah!
Wow, this is nuts!
Our dinner became dinner became dinner!
Even better!
Let's roll it in!
Does that thing look like
it'll fit on the deck, Loopy?
Hey, you think something's up?
The ship's all wobbly and
Loopy and Usopp are screaming!
I swear, I can't leave those
idiots alone for ten minutes.
One sword style, 360 caliber Phoenix!
Nice one, Zoro!
What's all the noise about?
Hey, look, Sanji!
We just caught a fish!
Yeah, I see that.
Good job, guys.
Can't say I've ever
cooked anything that big.
This should be fun.
But, uh, looks like you got cooked.
And I haven't even told you the best part!
There's a giant fish inside of it
with a giant fish inside of it!
I'm more concerned about
the ship, actually.
It kind of feels like we might be sinking.
Nah, we're fine.
Huh?
What's that thing over there?
It's some kind of sea snake!
Awesome!
Get closer, we can eat that too!
I think we got more than enough! Wait.
I know what that is.
That's Whitestrom.
It's a massive whirlpool that
appears suddenly in the deep sea.
Like a liquid sea monster!
That looks pretty crazy
What have they done now?
Oh no, that must be the Whitestrum.
They say that whenever a
ship gets caught inside it,
it'll be found somewhere far away.
Usually without its crew.
I know what that means.
They all died somewhere at sea.
We have to go, it's way too dangerous!
So they ended up somewhere
totally different, huh?
Cool!
I say we jump in and see where we go!
I don't think so!
Hurry!
We have to get away from
the whirlpool right now!
Okay!
You heard the navigator!
It's change or course or die!
Is that a giant fish?
Uh-huh!
Plus two more!
Stupid argue!
We'll never be able to move upward
if we're pulling that huge thing!
Great!
Now it's caught in the whirlpool!
Hurry!
We can't lose the food! Yeah! Forget it!
We're letting it go! No!
What about our dinner?
Well, if you get us all killed,
we'll never eat dinner again!
I can't believe you got into this much
trouble in the ten minutes I left you alone!
What is wrong with you?
Franky, use your coo to burst!
Sorry, but it's super
too late for that now!
Don't laugh at your own joke!
Crap, we are so dead!
Join the club!
Here it goes!
Oh no, it's too late!
I don't want to die!
Just hold on tight, guys!
it's over now wait a sec
what's this big black wall
that sounds like singing i think it's a
Hey!
Look at those scars!
Tell you what, after me and my
friends travel the Grand Line,
we'll come back here and find you.
Laboon!
You have to wait for us here
and mine crocus, Laboon.
Don't worry, we'll be back. I promise.
Laboon.
Look at how much you've grown.
Come on.
That's not Laboon.
He's supposed to be in the first
half of the Grand Line, remember?
That whale's way too big to fit
through the hole in the red line, see?
Amazing.
They're island whales.
Sing an entire pod is
extraordinarily rare.
That's weird.
Some of them have scars on their faces.
That look exactly like
the ones Laboon had.
I noticed that too.
I can't believe it.
Laboon's really not here.
Hand her off, I love the crew.
It's time to jump out things as proof.
Lapoon, don't go.
Please listen to me.
It's me, Brooke, from the Rumbar Pirates.
I'm your old friend. Easy, Brooke.
You gotta step out of it, buddy.
That's not the same
whale, okay? Let the boat!
Hey, we didn't come
here for whale watching.
We just escaped from
a dangerous whirlpool.
I'm gonna call Roll to make sure
everybody's safe and accounted for, okay?
Where's Nami? Here.
What about Robin? Over here. Good.
Now let's get out of here.
We don't want those whales
crashing into the Sunny.
We'll have to be careful.
Did you forget somebody? Yay, Sunny!
Not that you care, but the other six
crew members are still alive too.
What's the plan, Nami?
Let's not do anything.
All right, the lady says
not to do anything for now.
Feel free to go back to whale watching.
What is wrong with you?
Those whales are so big,
they're creating a current.
It's not safe to go against it.
We'll go the same way as them.
Let's catch a ride on their current!
Tighten the sails! Okay!
Wait a moment.
Didn't Laboon come from
this part of the sea?
Perhaps you might be Laboon's relatives!
Brooke, be careful.
Are any of you looking for a
calf who was lost 50 years ago?
Well, he's still alive!
He's living happily on the
other side of the world!
Don't worry!
According to my friend Luffy,
Laboon's gotten a lot bigger
since the last time we met!
So there's no need to be concerned!
He wouldn't want that!
Catch the dream!
Yo-ho-ho,
gather up all of the crew, it's
time to ship out Binks' crew,
sea wind glows to where, who
knows, the waves will be our guide,
or across the ocean's tide,
rays of sunshine far and wide,
birds they sing of cheerful
things in circles passing by.
Bid farewell to Weaverstown.
Say so long to Port Renown.
Sing a song, it won't be long.
Before we're casting off.
Across the gold and silver seas.
A salty spray puts us at ease.
Day and night to our delight.
The voyage never ends.
Gather up all of the crew.
It's time to ship out Vince's crew.
Pirates, we eternally
are challenging the sea.
With the waves to rest our heads.
Ship beneath us as our beds.
Hoisted high upon the mast.
Our jolly Roger flies.
Somewhere in the endless sky.
Stormy winds are blowing by.
Waves are dancing.
He's giving us a ride!
How about that?
They're heading up for two.
Now this is what I call
traveling in style.
So pound your feet and clap your hands.
Till Sunday's return.
Yo-ho-ho.
Ah, New Feat?
Hey!
Ready, crew?
Count down with me!
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one!
We made it!
Look at the world!
We did it, everybody!
It's really bad weather!
Look at that lightning!
The winds are raging!
Yeah, the water's rough, too!
The needle's going crazy! Let's go!
Woo-hoo!
That doesn't look right. The sea!
It's on fire!
How fascinating!
Cool!
There's a volcano and everything!
Calm down, Luffy! Listen!
None of the needles are pointing there!
Something's up!
Even for the new world,
this island is bad news!
That's not what the volcano says!
The island is right there!
Who cares about some dumb needles?
We go where we want!
What's gonna stop us? The fire!
We can't get any closer than this!
The sea is literally burning!
What's so funny?
Sparks.
The ship's gonna catch fire! No way!
You super underestimate the sunning!
There's something wrong about this place.
Just look!
The fish are dead!
They're bones!
Bones!
And what is wrong with that, Braytel?
Uh...
Hey, this is weird.
They don't normally cry.
What's wrong, buddy?
Does your stomach hurt?
No, that's a distress signal.
Someone close by is calling for help.
If I pick it up, can I hear them?
Wait, Luffy.
More than half of those calls are fake.
This is likely just a trap.
The Navy often uses this as a
trick to hunt down pirate ships.
Once you pick up, they can determine your
location and launch a surprise attack.
Thank you, Robin.
That's great advice.
I'm sure our captain has
other things to do than...
Hello?
My name is Monkey D.
Luffy, and I'm gonna
be king of the pirates!
You don't need to tell them all that!
Someone help! What's
wrong? Please! It's cold!
We need boss!
It's real hot where we
are, and who's boss?
My friends are getting cut down!
One after another!
The samurai is gonna kill us!
The what now?
Wait, uh, who? Samurai?
And where are you?
Please hurry!
We're on the island of...
Punk Hazard!
We don't have much time left!
He's dead! Terrible!
Mmm.
Smells like trouble's brewing out there.
What do you mean it's brewing?
He's dead!
It's already brewed!
This is scary!
Maybe he was acting and
this is just a trap.
So cold!
Oh, you're so cold!
A samurai's like a
swordsman, right, Brooke?
Yes, from a faraway land, an island
known as the Kingdom of Wano.
Wano is closed off from the rest of the
world, so most people know little about it.
In fact, it's not even affiliated
with the world government.
They say that their
samurai are so formidable
that even the navy dares
not challenge them.
The legendary owner of this blade,
Shusui, may have long since fallen,
but its story does not end here.
With you as its master, this
sword will surely be satisfied.
This body of a legendary samurai—how
shameful of me to allow it to no defeat!
I
never even heard of
the place, but he said,
"punk hazard, not the place
with the samurai." samurai
You think that's it right there?
I think that's a logical conclusion.
Those portable transponder snails
have a limited signal area.
Come on!
Fight through the fire and help him!
We'll die!
He's dead anyway!
And there's a samurai!
He sounds scary!
I agree!
Please hurry!
We're on the island of...
Puck Hazard!
We don't have much time left!
That was Luffy! No doubt!
Not ideal, but at least we know
where the Straw Hats ended up.
Makes enough sense with the battle at
Fishman Island and what took place after.
The only question now is, did they answer
the call for help or did they move on?
You guys are the Navy?
Can't you just send me to jail?
I'll do anything, what
the hell do you want?
We want you nice and crispy.
Would you stop that already?
I warned you before, to Sigi—let's
change course for Punk Hazard—hold!
On smoker, it's deserted,
right after the incident,
four years ago—they sealed
off the entire island.
Surely no one's there anymore?
Maybe they're not.
Frankly, I can't imagine anyone
surviving in that living hell,
but we're screwed if we're
wrong—change course immediately!
Men, we're off to Punk
Hazard. Huh, you sure?
Vice
admiral, that place is off
limits even for folks like us.
You don't get to lecture me while
burning a man alive—come on!
a man alive come on
Yes, sir.
That settles it, then.
Just don't die. Yeah, you wish.
This should be fun. Aren't fatal?
You won?
Good job, Usopp.
You wanna go?
Trade with me, please!
Take this.
It's a giant shellfish lunchbox. Woo-hoo!
Yeah, I can't wait!
Milky Road, let's go!
That's cool!
You sure showed that wall of fire!
You can make them just like
they do in Skypiea now, huh?
Uh-huh.
We still have to wait a minute
before they stabilize, though.
Okay!
All right, time for adventure, you guys.
Come on, Lady Mary.
Be careful.
Please don't die.
Wish I could go, you lucky punks.
They'll probably need
our help soon enough.
Watch out for lava.
Usopp, be brave.
Someone trade with me.
Oh, this shellfish is great.
Don't tell me you're
eating your lunch already.
Ooh, look over the edge,
there's fire! Fire! This is fun!
Usopp, you're scared over nothing.
Will these clouds still be
here when we need to come back?
Hey, and it's still raining, too.
Island scouting weather.
No, it's not!
Nami, are you certain that cloud
bridge of yours reaches the island?
I have no idea.
I couldn't have handled that.
Not with all my fur.
I'm hot enough already.
I'll bet this will work out fine.
Robin's there.
We just needed one person on
the team to keep Luffy in line.
Sounds like you cooked up
a whole formula for this.
You're so considerate, Nami.
Let me make a dessert for you.
Maybe something nice and cool?
Yay! Dessert!
It's not for you!
They've got a gate and everything.
Wonder if there's a town.
Not likely.
Whoever lived here before
probably got burned to a crisp.
If there was a town,
then it would be on fire.
Wherever that call came from,
it must have been far away,
safe from all of this mess.
Robin, back me up.
I was skeptical at first,
but the flavor is great.
Why is everyone eating
their lunch right now?
You're not?
I'll eat it for you.
I'm saving it for later.
My disease is coming back.
I can feel it inside of me.
So here's the thing.
I've got can't go on this island
disease, and it's terminal.
Oh, no. I know. Oh, no.
Well, that settles it.
This is where the call came from.
Yeah?
He said punk hazard for sure.
Get Mini Mary away from all that fire.
So this is the right island, but that
distress call could have come from anywhere.
How curious.
Seems the island is off limits.
Yeah, Luffy, see that?
Yeah? So?
I love danger. Not that.
The world government, Mark.
They're running this place.
So whoever it was that
called for help was a marine.
It's obviously a trap.
I guess we're done here, right, guys?
It's hot.
Hey, stop trespassing is a crime—are
you sure you want to do this?
Oh wait, yeah, I guess we're
already criminals aren't we?
But the government you don't want
to pick a fight with them, do you?
Wait, we've done that too. Okay,
but from a morality standpoint
that is stupid—why is it so hot?
I'm thinking because
everything is on fire.
I doubt it's always been this way since
the government built a fence here.
Something happened,
but what
it's not
so
bad—those aren't houses,
clearly there's some sort of
government research facilities.
So you think the volcano or something
did this and then what they shut
the whole operation down or do you
think they were up to something?
And they did this—the fact that the log
post didn't point to
this island troubles me.
But what does that mean?
what does that mean
Hey!
Did that samurai kill you?
If you're not dead yet, say so!
Hey! Samurai!
You wanna fight?
He's a killer!
He'll kill us too!
Now you have an appetite.
This is stress-eating, thank you!
Well, there's something else
about this that's fishy.
The guy making the emergency
call said it was cold, didn't he?
Please! It's cold!
We need Buzz! Yeah, he did.
But how can he be cold and on fire?
Maybe he's stupid.
I don't, that's the issue here!
Can there be a cold place
on a burning island?
Or perhaps he was cold simply
because he was bleeding to death.
Robin, can you keep
those stars to yourself?
This is nice and cold, too.
The sky on the far side of the island
is different than the sky on our side.
Almost like the weather is the
complete opposite over there.
Not our problem, I guess.
It's a giant!
It's way bigger than that.
My goodness.
Oh wow!
Those things are real? Crazy!
No way!
Whatever this is, it must be a trick.
Those things are only in fairy tales.
And yet, just look at it.
What else could it possibly be?
A dragon?
You